channelv.in 2014-10-08

# Channel V - India Youth GEC Tv Channel| Youth Base Tv Shows

 **Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy covers the information Star India Private Limited (“STAR” and/or “We”) collects from the user(s) (“User(s)” and/or “You”) of http://channelv.in (“Website”). This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with the Terms of Use of the Website.

Here are our privacy principles:

    Providing information to us is your choice.

    You can choose to have the Personal Information provided by You deleted.

    You always have the ability to opt-out of receiving communications from us.

**Information Collection and Use:**

The information which You may provide to us and/or which we may collect from You could be the following:

    Personal information such as your name, password, e-mail ID, address, phone number, photographs, videos, resume or such similar information (“Personal Information”);

    Feedback, comments, reviews and any other similar content uploaded by the Users on the Website;

    Details of usage of the Website;

    Details of the computer system or computer network which You use to visit the Website and undertake any activity on the Website.  
**  
Purpose:**

Our primary purposes in collecting information from You are to facilitate social networking on the Website, to showcase content produced by STAR, to obtain feedback in relation to the content on the Website and to keep You updated of the latest news and events in relation to the Website and Channel [V].

We may also use the information collected from You for transactional emails or to provide You with information, direct marketing, online and offline advertising and other materials regarding products, services and other offers from time to time in connection with STAR and/or its parent, subsidiary and affiliated companies (“STAR Entities”) and its joint ventures.

We collect details of User behavior and preferences for internal analytics from all Users of the Website. This information is collected through the use of server log files and tracking technologies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information and may include cookies and web beacons.

We may combine your Personal Information, other information and information collected from tracking technologies and aggregate it with information collected from other Users using our Website to attempt to provide You with a better experience on our Website.

You understand, agree and acknowledge that our collection, storage and processing of your Personal Information is for a lawful purpose connected with a function or activity of the STAR Entities and/or its joint ventures. You further understand, agree and acknowledge that your Personal Information which is classified as sensitive personal information as per applicable laws is considered necessary for the Website to provide various services on the Website to You and for Your usage of the Website.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure:**

STAR is the recipient of all the Personal Information and shall exercise reasonable commercial endeavors for the prevention of unauthorized disclosure of the Personal Information provided by the Users. We may enable access of the Users’ information to the STAR Entities or its joint ventures, agents or third parties in relation to the Website or for any other marketing related activity undertaken by or on behalf of the STAR Entities and/or its joint ventures. However, STAR will not include Personal Information received from the Users in any advertising creative. We will ensure on reasonable commercial efforts basis that the third parties and agents employed by us maintain confidentiality with respect to the Personal Information provided by the Users and use it strictly for the purposes specified herein.

If a User wishes to have all the information that he/she has provided to STAR deleted, he/she can always do so by sending a request to Us on the e-mail id provided at the bottom of the page.

If a complaint is received with respect to any information uploaded by a User for infringement of the rights of any person, We will investigate such complaint and promptly proceed to remove the information from display and delete the complained of information from our records if the complaint is found to be valid.

The name and address of the company that is collecting and retaining the information is:

Star India Pvt Ltd,  
Urmi Estate, 1st Floor,  
Urmi Estate,  
95, Ganpatrao Kadam Marg,  
Lower Parel, Mumbai-400 013

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement:**

STAR cooperates with mandated government and law enforcement agencies or with any third parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about You to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as We, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal processes, to protect the property and rights of the STAR Entities or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. STAR may also provide your Personal Information to various tax authorities upon any demand or request from them.

**Business Transfers:**

STAR may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will ensure that the Personal Information You have provided through the Website is stored and used by the transferee in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Email Policies:**

STAR may use the e-mail ID provided by You for the purposes mentioned in this Privacy Policy. You have full control regarding which of these emails You want to receive. If You decide at any time that You no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. Please note that once we receive your request, it may take an additional period of time for your opt-out to become effective.

**Security:**

STAR uses ordinary industry standard technology designed to help keep your Personal Information safe. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information You put in before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data We collect is protected against unauthorized access. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, We will employ commercially reasonable and practicable security practices and procedures and security methods and technologies. We will also ensure on reasonable commercial efforts basis that any agent or third party that We employ complies with the same security standards as us for the protection of your Personal Information.

Your information may be transferred to or be maintained on computers, computer systems and computer resources located outside of your state or country where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those where you live. If You are located outside India and choose to provide information to us, please be aware that STAR keeps or transfers information to India and processes it there. Your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure. Although We strive to protect your personal data, We cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once We have received your information, We have commercially reasonable procedures and security features in place to reasonably endeavor to prevent unauthorized access.

**Changes in Privacy Policy:**

From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website constitutes an acceptance of the then-current Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions so We encourage You to visit this page periodically to review any changes.

**Phishing:**

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to STAR. Safeguarding information to help protect You from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

**Contact Us:**

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of STAR or your dealings with the Website, You can contact us via the links at the bottom of the page, or by writing to hello@startv.com.

**Grievance Officer:**

Priyanka Agrawal shall be the Grievance Officer for the purpose of this Privacy Policy. If You have any question or grievance or want to delete or modify your Personal Information, You shall mark your correspondence to the email ID provided in the name of Priyanka Agrawal, Grievance Officer. Any communication which is not marked as such shall not be treated as a valid and binding communication for the purpose of this Privacy Policy and applicable laws.

This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules there under  as applicable and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.
